Dime Ilievski

dmc.graphics@protonmail.com

linkedin.com/in/dimethyl-cryptamine

Summary

Artist, designer and illustrator with more than 20 years of experience - specialized in hand drawn concept arts, paintings and masterpieces. Started at very young age, I've taken part in regional and international fine art exhibitions and won numberless diplomas, awards, and earned valuable experiences. Most precious to me, is the first diploma in fine arts that I've got when I was only four years old, and since age of thirteen, my interest in digital art has grown mostly because of the advantages that digital tools can provide, and the possibilities they're offering for an artist to express.

In my teenage years, I've been editing and reconstructing 3D models mostly for PC games and putting more effort in animation. Interested in UI/UX, I've been part of different teams where I was providing the necessary graphics for websites and games. During my academy studies, I got employed to sketch and draw a storyboard for a movie, a project that has taken two years.

My skills development continued with the evolution of mobile phones and the emerging of mobile applications, where I've contributed with UI for Android apps, creating game characters and various textures.

I've learned very helpful tricks and how to use my talented hand to convert physical art into digital form and create various unique designs in many styles.

With the boom of the internet and it's commonly used social platforms, I'm designing and illustrating banners, logos and DP for individuals, companies and businesses.

My interest in human psychology and esoteric knowledge had lead me into the mathematics and geometry, and how shapes, colors and visuals in general can affect the mind of the observer - and that simply added efficiency in my designs, specially to those for commercial use.

Experience

Carpentry designer

SILVERCRAFT LIMITED

May 2019 - Feb 2021 (1 year 10 months)

Designing wooden molds for production of items made of fiberglass.

Storyboard Artist

Bojan Perin

Aug 2014 - Nov 2016 (2 years 4 months)

Creating a storyboard for a full length action/comedy movie based on the scenario written by Bojan Perin.

Graphic Illustrator

Freelance

Graphic Designer

Six Spikes Studio
May 2022 - Present (2 months +)

Education

Univerzitet 'Sv. Kiril i Metódij' vo Skopje

Ethnic, Cultural Minority, Gender, and Group Studies Aug 2009 - Sep 2012

Skills

Sketching • Digital Illustration • Art • Concept Art • Fine Art • Illustration • Graphic Arts • Graphic Design • Print Design • Hand Drafting

Honors & Awards

Statement of gratitude - Bureau for Development of Education & CRS (Catholic

Relief Services)

Jun 2002

Statement of gratitude for participating in the program "We, the people - project citizen"

Statement of gratitude - O.U. "Lazo Angelovski" - Skopje

Jun 1999

Statement of gratitude for contributing to the improvement and affirmation of the institution.

Statement of gratitude - O.U. "Lazo Angelovski" - Skopje

Feb 1998

Statement of gratitude for contributing to the improvement of the work of the institution.